=========================
=HELL-FORGED Patch Notes=
=========================

(v1.00c update)

►Added some additional textures.

►Added new switch textures to signify the more important switches.

►Map HF1M3 now has a Green skull-key that is used to get the Mauler atop the molten pillar.

►All unimportant locked rooms now no longer use the skull-key textures. Instead uses a colored square one.

►Aside from contextual secrets, metal-face switches are no longe used as generic switches to prevent confusion for decoration.

►Lowered the raised platforms in HF1M5's end arena so they don't block the player's movement.

►Made various changes disembodied switches so they announce what they did. Some secrets aren't as ambiguous.

►Made various maps slightly a bit more challenging.

►Added small details to better announce what key area the player is in.

►Fixed the Bloodfiend G4 frame that incorrectly uses the F4 frame's image.

►Fixed the 0,0 offset for the "M_Doom" title image.

►Fixed a bug in map HF1M3 where the Red skull-key wasn't needed to get the nailgun.

►Fixed some unused sectors and tags in various maps.

►Fixed various misc. map errors such as misaligned textures, lighting, etc.

►Fixed a bug that caused the Phantom's missile had the THRUGHOST flag.

►Fixed the intermission 'next map' sound from using the Doom weapon pickup sound.

►Fixed a bugged script in HF1M7's where the 3rd round of arena monsters wouldn't activated on Templar difficulty.

►Fixed a bug that caused the power-ups spawn in the water column in HF1M8 to drop. Now there is a secret room.